{
    "id": "9f53d3f9e72845938ad758fd382bb7ab",
    "title": "Always, Ever, Never",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Have you ..................... met my mother?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never",
                "ever",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "163cd2be949c4bb08b19d033a76b4376"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will ........................ remember you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "493b3386e5c546b8b24a98cbb2b5c73e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have loved him ........................ since I met him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6f62791210b3467495b2954dfef88799"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................... want to see you again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never",
                "ever",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef7c4579c0504b9391089939626f3046"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody ....................... visits them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "89352d7dc780421bbc6ea7de4ff936b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She will ....................... beg.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0ec89191402c4c19b499df3d89f09b87"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is the largest monument .................... built.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ce402c123aaf48e4aab2dd9b078ccbf5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had ....................... thought of getting married before I met Gautam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never",
                "ever",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f141b087abe34887ac327b8f78df59b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Has any woman ....................... managed to climb Everest in winter?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da29991222c445b7963e263ac23ed32b"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the best movie you have .................. watched?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a67dace8de7c41be90fdd46f548123f1"
        }
    ]
}